<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title>AdiDoks</title>
    <subtitle>AdiDoks is a Zola theme helping you build modern documentation websites, which is a port of the Hugo theme Doks for Zola.</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://adidoks.netlify.com/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://adidoks.netlify.com"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2021-05-01T08:20:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://adidoks.netlify.com/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Research Experience</title>
        <published>2021-05-01T08:20:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-05-01T08:20:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://adidoks.netlify.com/docs/getting-started/research-experience/"/>
        <id>https://adidoks.netlify.com/docs/getting-started/research-experience/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://adidoks.netlify.com/docs/getting-started/research-experience/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-year-project-research-decomposition-of-noised-signal-python&quot;&gt;Final Year Project Research: Decomposition of Noised Signal (Python)&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conducted comprehensive research utilizing Singular Spectrum Analysis (SSA) and its derivatives for signal decomposition and noise reduction. Innovated Adaptive-TSVD and introduced Slid-SSA to enhance computational efficiency. Employed Sparse Autoencoder - Radial Basis Function Networks, and provided critical insights into the decomposition outcomes of large time signal dataset. The findings contributed to the academic understanding of signal processing and offered innovative approaches to the examination of periodic features within complex time series.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;quantitative-measurements-of-neural-signal-synchronization-matlab&quot;&gt;Quantitative Measurements of Neural Signal Synchronization (MATLAB)&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Implemented advanced neural signal processing techniques, utilizing a non-linear time series approach with singular spectrum analysis, enhanced by ISI- and SPIKE-Distance to reveal local characteristics. Introduced Non-Linear Interdependence (NLI) methods to quantify neural synchronization across brain regions, applied parameter-free measures for spike train synchrony, and innovatively modified and repaired SPIKE-Distance methodology, enabling precise monitoring of time-resolved synchrony in continuous data, reflecting a substantial contribution to the field.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;button onclick=&quot;window.history.back();&quot;&gt;Back&lt;&#x2F;button&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Startup Experience</title>
        <published>2021-05-01T08:20:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-05-01T08:20:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://adidoks.netlify.com/docs/getting-started/startup/"/>
        <id>https://adidoks.netlify.com/docs/getting-started/startup/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://adidoks.netlify.com/docs/getting-started/startup/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;company-profile&quot;&gt;Company Profile&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MeshX is a data intelligence service provider focused on serviceless computing, relying on user digital assets and algorithms as the core of the enterprise data management platform, dedicated to providing customer companies with low development costs, maintenance-free, on-demand scalability of serverless technology scenario-based applications.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;product-description&quot;&gt;Product Description&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company&#x27;s first educational SaaS product, wisdom winnow, is designed to provide interactive learning solutions for students on the A-Level international curriculum. Relying on its leading technology, wisdom winnow provides users with an integrated online course, cloud-based notes, algorithmic push, interactive testing, personalized assessment and other key functional modules, providing students with a unique learning solution for thousands of students. At present, a strategic partnership has been reached between wisdom winnow and E-Learning for interactive course recording, database construction, difficulty level analysis and other construction work. In the future, it will actively explore international courses and exams such as AP, IB, GRE and GMAT, and build an integrated study abroad solution.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;job-description&quot;&gt;Job Description&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsible for the construction of the company&#x27;s product demand solution and feasibility study of operation strategy; analyze existing competing products in the market, structure and integrate market demand and expectation; coordinate with R&amp;amp;D, sales and customer personnel to carry out internal confirmation and acceptance of product projects.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;button onclick=&quot;window.history.back();&quot;&gt;Back&lt;&#x2F;button&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Zhengqi Wang</title>
        <published>2021-05-01T08:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-05-01T08:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://adidoks.netlify.com/docs/getting-started/introduction/"/>
        <id>https://adidoks.netlify.com/docs/getting-started/introduction/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://adidoks.netlify.com/docs/getting-started/introduction/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;short-bio&quot;&gt;Short Bio&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a graduate student specializing in Electrical and Computer Engineering at &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;duke.edu&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Duke University&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, I have honed my analytical skills and proficiency in execution, particularly in numerical optimization applications. My education has revolved around leveraging data-driven methodologies to devise practical, actionable solutions, providing better work and life for human beings.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My experiences as a quantitative research intern at &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.mycapital.net&#x2F;&quot;&gt;MY Capital&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; and a risk modeling intern at &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;en.cicc.com&#x2F;&quot;&gt;CICC&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; have deepened my understanding of risk management, strategic trade development, and the analysis of predictive parameters. I have developed a comprehensive technical skill set and gained insights into the complex interplay between technology and finance. I am eager to collaborate with professionals who are equally passionate about advancing the fields of trading, quantitative research, and engineering. My goal is to contribute to a professional network where collective effort leads to significant advancements and practical solutions in our industry.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;academic-research&quot;&gt;Academic Research&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One page summary of my former research experience. &lt;a href=&quot;..&#x2F;research-experience&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Research→&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;startup-experience&quot;&gt;Startup Experience&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some detail info about my start upcompany. &lt;a href=&quot;..&#x2F;startup&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Startup→&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;button onclick=&quot;window.history.back();&quot;&gt;Back&lt;&#x2F;button&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Aaran Xu</title>
        <published>2021-04-01T08:50:45+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-04-01T08:50:45+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://adidoks.netlify.com/authors/aaran-xu/"/>
        <id>https://adidoks.netlify.com/authors/aaran-xu/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://adidoks.netlify.com/authors/aaran-xu/">&lt;p&gt;Creator of &lt;strong&gt;AdiDoks&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;github.com&#x2F;aaranxu&quot;&gt;@aaranxu&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
